tamigo.com 2019-08-18

# tamigo – Privacy Policy

Last updated 16th of July 2018 

1\. What this policy covers 

Your privacy is important to us, and so is being transparent about how we collect, use, and handle information about you. This policy is intended to help you understand what information is collected by **tamigo** , what we use it for, and how we handle and secure it. This Privacy Policy covers the information we collect about you when you use our website and services.

This policy also explains your choices about how we use information about you. Your choices include how you can object to certain uses of information about you and how you can access and update certain information about you. If you do not agree with this policy, please refrain from accessing and using our website and services. 

**Definitions used in this Privacy Policy**

**Website:** our main homepage – http://www.tamigo.com   
**Services:** our applications (web, Touch, smartphone apps), as well as support and integrations.   
**Subscription Account:** trial or paid account representing the customer and all data belonging to the customer.   
**Account Subscriber:** person or company who signed up for a trial or paid Subscription Account and are owners/managers of this account.   
**Email Subscriber:** recipient of marketing materials and messages.   
**Service Messages:** information sent out or generated pertaining to use of the Subscription Account.   
**tamigo, we, us:** **tamigo** and our franchisees. 

2\. What information we collect about you 

We collect information about you when you provide it to us directly or indirectly when you browse our website or use our services. 

2.1. Information you provide to us 

**Account and profile information**

We ask for and collect personal information such as your name, phone number and email address, as well as the company name when a trial subscription account is being created. We also ask for and collect personal data such as the email and name of the individuals you authorise to log into and use our services in connection with your subscription account. If you chose to purchase **tamigo** services and become a paid account subscriber, additional information is required in order to issue invoices. This information includes VAT no., invoice address, invoice email, contact email and reference.

As an account subscriber, you have additional options to provide more detailed personal and financial information. By voluntarily providing us with personal information, you give consent that you are the controller of such information or otherwise have requisite consent to provide it to us. For an overview of what information can be stored in **tamigo** , please refer to Annex A of this Privacy Policy.

If you are an individual who interacts with an account subscriber via **tamigo** and would like to make modifications to your personal data, please contact the account subscriber directly.

If you chose to become an email subscriber in order to receive news and marketing materials from **tamigo** , you will need to provide us with a valid email address. 

**Information you provide through our support channels**

The services also include our customer support, where you can choose to submit information regarding a problem you are experiencing or a question you may have regarding our services. You may be asked to provide the customer (subscription account) name, your contact details and any relevant information regarding the case, in order for the supporter to be able to investigate the question faster and get back to you with an answer. 

2.2. Information we automatically collect when you use our services 

**Logs regarding your use of our services**

As is the case with most websites and services, we gather and log certain information when you use our services. Examples of such collected data include login timestamps, changes to data of the subscription account and timestamps of such changes. We also store pseudonymised information about accessed URLs within our services, but this information is only available for 90 days. 

**Device and connection information**

We collect some basic information about the devices used to access our services. This device information includes your IP address and browser type. If you use our mobile applications, we also collect device information. 

Cookies in **tamigo** are used to provide functionality and optimise performance of the services. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for more details. 

2.3 Integrating other services with your subscription account 

You can choose to set up an integration between our services and other service providers you may be using. Such integrations can include exchanges of personal or financial data – import, update and export. We will perform integrations on behalf of the account subscriber owner and expect other service providers to be authorised by the account subscriber to handle such data transfers.

Information that is collected during the execution of integrations include the timestamp of execution, transfer endpoint, transfer status and response message returned from the other service. If the integration involves a file transfer, the contents of the integration files are kept for 90 days.

3\. How we use the information we collect 

We may use the information we collect about you (including personal information, to the extent applicable) to provide services and support, and to optimise the performance of our website and services. 

**To provide, maintain and improve services**

We use information about the usage of **tamigo** services in order to track and optimise performance, and to investigate any potential issues. We use the provided financial information to provide more advanced features for workforce planning and to optimise integrations with payroll systems. 

**To enable you to access and use services**

An email address is needed to access **tamigo** services. An email address or phone number is needed for you to be able to reset your password. If you wish to be able to log in to the smartphone app automatically, we will store your device token in **tamigo**. 

The following information is mandatory in order to be able to process the payments for your subscription account:

— Company name 

— VAT no. 

— Invoice address 

— Invoice email 

— Contact email 

— Reference 

The following information may be required based on your payment preference:

— Customer contact 

— EAN number 

— Order reference 

— Customer reference 

**To communicate with you about the services**

We use your contact information to send service information, such as action confirmations or notifications that arise from the use of services.

While your subscription account is in the trial period, we will contact you to provide assistance and promote services. Once the trial period is expired, we may follow up by phone or email within 12 months after the expiration date. If you do not wish to be contacted, please inform us by sending an email to [ support@tamigo.com](mailto:%20support@tamigo.com).

**To send promotional information**

We may send promotional communications to you via email, such as providing you with information about services via newsletters. You can opt out of receiving marketing communications from us by clicking “Unsubscribe” at the bottom of the email message at any time. 

**For safety and security, and to provide you with insights into the use of services**

Upon your request, we may investigate information stored in the subscription account, as well as related log data in order to provide you with information about data flows and the use of services by you or individuals authorised to access data in the subscription account. 

We may access information in your subscription account to resolve technical issues you encounter and also to respond to your requests for assistance. We store the information in our support tool Zendesk. 

**To protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights**

Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory and audit functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business. 

We use information about you where you have given us consent to do so for a specific purpose not listed above. 

**Legal basis for processing (for EU/EEA users only)**

If you are an individual in the European Economic Area (EEA), we collect and process information about you only where we have legal basis for doing so under applicable EU laws. The legal basis depends on the services you use and how you use them. This means we collect and use your information only in the following cases:

— We need it to provide you with services, including to operate the services and provide customer support. 

— It satisfies a legitimate interest (which is not overridden by your data protection interests) to protect our legal rights and interests. 

— You give us consent to do so for a specific purpose. 

— We need to process your data to comply with a legal obligation. 

If you have consented to our use of information about you for a specific purpose, you have the right to change your mind at any time. Please note that this does not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent before its withdrawal. 

4\. How we handle the information we collect 

**tamigo** does not transfer information to third parties, unless specifically instructed to do so by the subscriber. 

**Integrations with third parties**

If requested by the subscriber, data from the subscription account may be transferred to specified third parties. These kinds of integrations typically include one or more of the following data types: payroll, financial, attendance, personal or health data. It is up to the subscriber to decide what data should be shared with which third party, for how long, and when such sharing should take place.

As the integration only happens upon the request of an account subscriber, it is the responsibility of the account subscriber to check that the third-party systems are authorised to handle the data they receive.

We work with third-party service providers that provide hosting and maintenance of our services, application development, backup, storage, analytics, SMS, email and other services. These third-party service providers may, upon our request, have access to or process your personal information for the purpose of providing these services for us. We do not permit our third-party service providers to use the personal information we share with them for their marketing purposes or for any other purpose than in connection with the services they provide to us.

You can find a list of our service providers in our Data Processing Agreement on our Trust Centre.

**Compliance with enforcement requests and applicable laws and enforcement of our Rights**

In exceptional circumstances, we may share information about you with a third party if we believe that sharing is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, including to meet national security requirements, (b) enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) protect the security or integrity of our products and services, (d) protect **tamigo** , our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, or (e) respond to an emergency which we believe requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person. 

5\. How we store and secure the information we collect 

5.1. Information storage and security 

Depending on the customer’s physical location, the subscription account information may be stored in one of two locations: for customers located in Australia, subscription account information is stored in Australia, and for all other customers data is stored in the EU. This is the case for all data submitted by users of a particular subscription account, as well as the logs that arise from using **tamigo** services.

We use service providers for SMS, email and support functionality. These service providers are all based in and store data in the EU/EAA.

5.2. How long we keep information 

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information, as described in further detail below. 

**Account subscriber information**

If you choose to suspend your account, data provided to create a paid subscription account (refer to 2.1. Account and profile information) will remain in **tamigo**. 

**Subscription account data**

We retain your account data for as long as you have a paid subscription. If we do not receive payments for 30 days after the due date, your account will be deactivated.

If you choose to terminate the subscription, your data will be removed 90 days after the expiration of the subscription.

6\. How to access and control your information 

You have certain choices available to you when it comes to your information. Below is a summary of those choices, how to exercise them and any limitations. 

**Access and update your information**

In order to receive an overview or correct information used to process invoices, please contact [ debitor@tamigo.com](mailto:%20debitor@tamigo.com).

If you have been provided access to a subscription by a subscriber, you can access your information by logging in to our services on https://app.tamigo.com. Some additional information that you provided to the account subscriber may be stored, and to gain an overview of this information you need to contact the account subscriber directly.

As an account subscriber, you can see and manage all information that you provided to us directly by logging in to our services on https://app.tamigo.com.

As an account subscriber, if you no longer wish to use our services, please contact [ support@tamigo.com](mailto:%20support@tamigo.com) to assist you with the termination of your account. If access to a subscription has been provided to you by an account subscriber, please contact the account subscriber directly to deactivate your account. 

Our services give you the ability to delete certain information about you from within the service. For example, you can remove content that contains information about you, and you can remove certain profile information within your profile settings. Please note, however, that we may need to retain certain information for record-keeping purposes, to complete transactions, or to comply with our legal obligations. 

**Opt-out of communications**

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from us by using the unsubscribe link within each email. Even after you opt out from receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive transactional messages from us regarding our services. You can opt out of some notification messages in your account settings. 

We can assist an account subscriber in extracting all data stored on individuals. For information about such requests refer to our Data Processing Agreement on our Trust Centre.

If you have received access to **tamigo** via an account subscriber and want to retrieve, modify or remove your information, please contact the account subscriber directly.

7\. Other important privacy information 

Many of our products are intended for use by organisations. Where the services are made available to you through an organisation (e.g. your employer), that organisation is the administrator of the services and is responsible for the accounts and/or service sites over which it has control. If this is the case, please direct your data privacy questions to your administrator, as your use of the services is subject to that organisation's policies. We are not responsible for the privacy or security practices of an administrator's organisation, which may be different than this policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you directly when we have made significant changes to our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review our privacy policy whenever you use our services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy, you will need to stop using the services and deactivate your account(s), as outlined above.

Annex A: Data types stored in **tamigo**

**Contact information:**

— Email address 

— Phone number 

— Home address 

**Employee personal data:**

— Full name 

— Wage number 

— Social security number 

— Gender 

— Birthdate 

— Absence 

— Car license plate number 

— Bank account information 

**Employment data:**

— Employee’s start and end date 

— Position 

— Salary 

— Planned and actual shifts and hours 

— Bonus payouts 

— Drive registrations 

**Company financial data:**

— Revenue 

— Budget 

**Department IP address**

**Documents:**

— Employee contracts 

— Profile picture 

**Integration credentials**

You also have the possibility to define other fields to store in **tamigo**.
